[siren blaring]
[swallows]
[breathing deeply]
[groans]
[officer 1] Your friend?
Can you explain
what you mentioned earlier?
Well, there's a kid
whose name is Oh Beom-seok.
He goes to Byuksan High School,
over there.
- [officer 1] Oh Beom-seok?
- [Yeong-i] Yes. He called me to a café.
- But he wasn't there by himself.
- Yeong-a.
[gasps] Are you okay?
Are you all right?
Where'd the other students go?
I was the only one there.
- [gasps]
- Listen, it's all right, okay?
You can be honest with us.
You can trust us.
[sighs] I was there alone.
Stop lying.
Don't tell
Su-ho about what happened today.
[Yeong-i gasps] What?
[Su-ho] Hey, Yeon Si-eun.
Hey, Si-eun-a.
[sighs]
[tapping]
[phone buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
[Si-eun] Beom-seok-a.
[poignant music playing]
Yeah?
It's time to stop.
Stop messing with Su-ho.
[breathing shakily]
[phone bleeps]
[siren blaring]
[sighs]
[music fades]
["Hero" by Meego playing]
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
DIVIDING NUMBERS WITH TWO AND THREE DIGITS
[Si-eun's father] Honey,
I just asked what you were doing
while he was out getting hurt.
What's wrong with that?
[mother] You're not the only busy one.
Do you think I just relax at home
while you're out training and competing?
You said you wanted to work together.
You said you'd help raise our kid well.
It was your idea to have a kid
in the first place.
I thought it would be easy!
He always gets hurt.
- I thought that he would be a normal kid.
- [mother scoffs]
[sighs]
Uh, uh… Si… Si… Si-eun-a.
Si-eun-a.
[poignant music playing]
Open the door, Si-eun-a. Talk to me.
[mother] Si-eun-a,
will you open the door? Hmm?
- [father] Si-eun-a.
- [knocking]
Open the door, Si-eun-a.
Talk to me, please?
[mother sighs]
- [knocking]
- [father] Yeon Si-eun.
Mom and Dad weren't fighting.
We were just talking.
- Si-eun-a.
- [knocking]
[father] Si-eun-a. Yeon Si-eun.
[mother] Si-eun-a.
[father] Si-eun-a.
[poignant music continues]
[father] It's all right.
Tell me the truth.
[music fades]
Was it the same jerks
who punched your face last time?
[Si-eun sighs]
I'm telling the truth.
I fell down the stairs.
I don't believe that's what happened.
Why were you there?
No reason.
[sighs]
I'm going to transfer you
to another school.
That's all there is to it.
- I don't want to.
- You don't what?
Why are you being like that?
I mean,
it's hard enough raising you by myself.
- Why won't you listen?
- Hey, Dad.
I've been kinda wondering.
How come you're so interested
in my life all of a sudden?
What?
[sighs] Nothing.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[alarm bleeping]
[camera shutters clicking]
[Jin-won laughs]
[phone buzzes]
Yes?
Beom-seok-kun is here at home.
How did it go?
The Seocho Police Station will keep quiet.
And for his school,
I've already spoken to the principal.
The madam went to Jeju Island,
so keep an eye on him
and stay by his side.
Who knows what Beom-seok will do next?
He's being sent abroad.
Find him a school in the Philippines.
All right.
[phone bleeps]
[Beom-seok] How did you know?
Aide Park-nim told me
that I would find you in there.
[Beom-seok] About yesterday.
I got a call from the police.
Yeon Si-eun,
he wanted to let this incident go.
He said that he was your friend.
[teacher] What's important
is what they demanded.
In this revolt…
Someone wake him up.
- Everyone, stay awake.
- [boy 1] Hey, Su-ho.
Ahn Su-ho.
[teacher] Where did we leave off?
Why is no one answering me?
[Su-ho sighs]
[teacher] The class president should know.
[boy 2] The Japan-Korea Treaty of 1876.
[teacher] All right, then. In that case,
turn to page 109.
Let's learn about the Donghak Uprising.
[tense music playing]
Shall we begin?
To understand the Donghak Uprising,
first we have to learn
about the peasant forces…
[phone buzzing]
AHN SU-HO
SOMETHING CAME UP AT HOME
SO I CAN'T COME TO SCHOOL FOR A WHILE
[Su-ho] Where were you last night? Huh?
You ignored all my calls.
What?
[tense music continues]
Are you messing with me
for my birthday still?
Is that what's going on? Huh?
That's enough. It's not funny.
I'm not doing that.
Sorry about yesterday.
[doorbell chiming]
[tense music continues]
[chiming]
[sighs]
FINAL EXAM
IN 1 DAY
- [Jeong-chan] Whoa!
- [Tae-hun] What the hell?
- [boy 1] Hey.
- [Jeong-chan] Let's go for a smoke.
- [Tae-hun sighs] Damn it.
- [boy 1] What is that?
- [boy 2] Tell you later.
- [boy 1] Yeah, right.
[Tae-hun] Shit.
[sighs]
Why is Oh Beom-seok absent?
No idea.
Haven't you called him?
You guys are pretty tight.
His phone's turned off.
You know what's up?
- Tell him he owes me for the damages.
- Yeah, I know.
What?
What damages?
[sighs]
It cost 800,000 won.
If you don't pay me back,
I'll kill you, 'kay?
Answer me.
[Jeong-chan] Okay.
[phone buzzing]
JEONG-CHAN
- Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
- Damn it! Pick up your phone, Beom-seok.
- Please leave a message after the tone.
- Ahn Su-ho needs to be taught a lesson.
[boy 1] Hey, but why
isn't Yeon Si-eun at school?
[boy 2] Did he actually die?
- Yeong-bin was way over the line.
- Hey, what's with all this bullshit?
We'd all be attending his funeral
if he was dead, dude.
- Damn it.
- [phone bleeps]
- [ringing tone]
- Ah, man.
[Jeong-chan sighs]
[groans]
[yelps]
[coughs]
[groans]
Wait! Please wait.
Oh Beom-seok called you,
but you wouldn't pick up,
so he brought that girl over
to make you come meet us.
What?
[Jeong-chan] You know,
that girl who lives with you. But
we expected you instead. Not Yeon Si-eun.
[suspenseful music playing]
- And?
- [Jeong-chan] A… and…
Uh, Yeong-bin has this friend
who was paid by Oh Beom-seok
to beat you up.
Oh Beom-seok did everything.
None of this was us.
[Jeong-chan yelps]
[Yeong-i] What's going on?
Where is Si-eun hospitalized?
He went home today.
I'm sorry. It's all 'cause of me.
[Yeong-i sighs]
Hey!
Si-eun told me
I had to keep it a secret from you.
Stay out of trouble.
[doorbell chiming]
[Si-eun] Who is it?
[Su-ho] Delivery.
[clock ticking]
Hey, what's up?
[Su-ho] What do you mean, what's up?
I'm thirsty. Give me water.
[lock bleeps]
[chuckles]
You doing all right?
Sure. Yeah.
Why are you here?
I was just in the neighborhood.
Are you okay?
Why?
Tomorrow's finals. Coming to school?
Yeah.
I gotta study.
Okay, good.
See you in class.
[chuckles]
["9" by Han playing]
♪ I'm wearin' out discreetly… ♪
[lock bleeps]
♪ It's somewhere I need to go ♪
♪ Summer's gone and winter's comin' ♪
[music fades]
[door opens]
- Is he in his room?
- Yes, sir.
You little bastard!
You're nothing but fucking vermin.
[panting] I… told you not to do anything
that shits on my name.
You didn't listen.
- Huh? You little shit!
- [poignant music playing]
What's your goddamn problem?
I told you to do what I say,
barely breathe, and live a quiet life.
You're so pathetic. That was too hard?
Is that too hard? You shit, answer me.
Fucking loser!
You're such a fucking little bitch!
Whew! This fucking little bastard.
You…
Once you go study abroad,
you're free to do whatever
the hell you want.
Die from drugs, I don't give a shit.
Just never tell anyone
that you are my son. Understand?
Hey!
Keep an eye on this punk.
[door slams]
[shuddering]
I never asked to be your son.
[music fades]
[insects chirping]
Beom-seok-kun.
Fuck off! Damn it.
Hands off! Don't follow me.
[breathing heavily]
- [driver] Where are you headed?
- Just drive, please.
[phone chimes]
[phone buzzing]
MISSED CALL: SU-HO, JEONG-CHAN,
YEONG-BIN, TAE-HUN
SU-HO
IMAGE
ANSWER THE PHONE,
OR I WILL KILL YOUR FRIENDS
- [Yeong-bin wailing]
- [crunching]
[moans] Hey, wait.
[moans]
So you better…
[Yeong-bin gasps]
…get Oh Beom-seok.
I can't. I have no idea where he went.
He's not answering any of my calls.
- Ah, shit.
- [Su-ho] Punishment's the same, then.
[Yeong-bin gasps]
[phone buzzing]
[siren blaring in distance]
BEOM-SEOK
Where are you at?
Where are you, bitch-ass?
Why?
[Su-ho] Oh Beom-seok.
You better stop hiding.
[tense music playing]
[phone clatters]
[crunching]
[screams]
[groaning]
Oh shit, man.
[whimpering]
[phone bleeps]
OH BEOM-SEOK
Hey, what's up?
Ahn Su-ho's game on.
I'll pay.
[music fades]
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
Hey.
Have you been in touch with Su-ho?
Yeah, he stopped by earlier today.
Su-ho found out about that fight.
[Si-eun] What?
[Yeong-i] He's not at work,
and he's not picking up his phone.
Did he say anything to you?
Do you think
he went looking for Oh Beom-seok?
I'll try to call him.
[taps phone]
[phone bleeps]
[tense music playing]
[Su-ho] You filming a movie?
What the hell is this? Seriously.
Where's Oh Beom-seok?
It's been a while.
[Beom-seok sighs]
[sighs] I'm the one that you're mad at.
Why are you messing with the others?
What did they do wrong?
[Beom-seok sighs]
I'm sorry…
for hurting your feelings.
[Beom-seok sighs]
[Su-ho] I apologized to you.
Your turn to apologize
to Si-eun and Yeong-i.
No, thanks.
I have nothing to apologize for.
Please just do it.
I said no.
Then you'll get beaten
till you come to your senses.
[Woo-yeong] Hey, Ahn Su-ho.
Ah.
[chuckles]
Climb in.
Are you seriously paying
this asshole money
just to beat me up?
[sniffles]
[sighs]
You're really pathetic, you know that?
Gimme a sec. I need to warm up. [grunts]
[boy 1] Shit!
[yells] Oh shit!
[wails]
[all grunting]
- [grunts]
- [boy 2] Hey!
[boy 3 wails]
[boy 4 groans]
[thud]
I guess you're still workin' out.
Huh. Some people might think
you're still an athlete.
Do you not remember me kicking your ass?
Get in.
[sighs]
Well, the moment is finally here,
my hyeong-nims.
I told you I lost badly to this guy
back in middle school, right?
This fight
is going to be my revenge match.
Salute.
- [Jeong-chan] It's starting.
- [Tae-hun] Bet he can fight.
[Jeong-chan] For sure, whatever. Let's go.
Let's make the video fun. Yeah?
[Tae-hun] Please, Woo-yeong.
- You have to win. You're our only hope.
- [Su-ho] Talking shit?
[dramatic music playing]
- [boy 3] Oh no…
- [Tae-hun] What was that?
Ooh! Ooh.
Fuck, man, that was so close.
- [Jeong-chan] That's right!
- [Tae-hun] Whoo!
Your left leg's fucked up, huh?
- [Jeong-chan] Dude.
- What are you gonna do about it?
- [boys] Whoa! Whoa!
- [Woo-yeong] Oh shit.
- [Tae-hun] Behind you!
- [boy 1] Get up, Woo-yeong!
- [all shouting]
- [Woo-yeong] Damn it!
- [boy 1] Get up, get up!
- [Tae-hun] Come on! Woo-yeong!
- [Jeong-chan] You got this!
- [Tae-hun] Shit!
[Jeong-chan] Woo-yeong, hit him.
- [boy 2] Woo-yeong! Get your revenge!
- [boy 3] Kick his ass! His leg. Yes!
- Get it. Okay!
- [Tae-hun] Great job, Woo-yeong!
- [boy 2] Get him, Woo-yeong!
- [boy 3] Come on! You got this!
- [boy 2] Show your power! Shit!
- [boy 3] Come on, get him.
- [Tae-hun] Oh, fuck this!
- [boy 4] Let's go!
- [Su-ho] You got lucky.
- [Woo-yeong] Fuck you, asshole.
[Jeong-chan] There we go.
There we go! Oh my God, yeah!
- Killer punch!
- [Tae-hun] Yeah!
[Tae-hun] Go! Let's go!
- Kill him. Kill that fucking bastard.
- [boy 2] Let's go!
[Woo-yeong grunts]
That's not good.
What the fuck, dude?
[Woo-yeong] Hey! Eat shit!
[whooshing and high-pitched ringing]
[sounds fade]
[Jeong-chan] He's so fucked.
- Oh, look at that asshole.
- [boy 3] Yeah, dude.
- [all gasping]
- [Tae-hun] Fuck, man.
[Jeong-chan laughs] Okay.
- Man, that was a fucking fight.
- [Tae-hun] They're fucking crazy.
[breathing shakily]
Hey.
Who's the pathetic one now, shithead? Huh?
Huh?
Tell me what to do now, man.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
You're always looking down on me like…
like I'm a piece of shit.
Hey.
Will you please just wake up…
[sighs] …and stop blaming other people,
Beom-seok-a.
[sighs]
Hey.
Stop saying my fucking name,
you cocky shit.
Bitch. You son of a bitch.
[grunting] Damn it.
Hey, fuck this. Let's jump in.
- Son of a bitch! Cocky shit.
- [Tae-hun] Bastard!
- Fucking asshole.
- [boy 3] Asshole.
[Beom-seok] You're pathetic.
You son of a bitch.
- Stupid shithead.
- [gasping and grunting]
[Beom-seok] Fuck you.
- [boy 5 laughing]
- [boy 4] That's right, keep doing this!
- Shithead! Fucking bitch!
- [Beom-seok] Don't tell me what to do.
- [Jeong-chan] Eat it!
- [Tae-hun] Fucking asshole!
[Beom-seok] You son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch! Fuck you.
[panting]
You motherfucker. You shithead.
- [panting]
- [Jin-won's secretary] Beom-seok-kun.
[Aide Park shouts] Oh Beom-seok!
- [Beom-seok] Oh fuck.
- [Aide Park] Let's go.
[Beom-seok groans]
Don't touch me.
- Let's go.
- Stop. Stop!
Let fucking go of me, you fuck!
[secretary gasps]
[panting]
[sighs]
- [footsteps]
- [Jeong-chan] Ahn Su-ho.
Ahn Su-ho.
- Hey, this bastard's not breathing.
- [Tae-hun] What?
Ahn Su-ho.
[boy 1] Fuck.
- Oh fuck.
- [Tae-hun] Fuck.
If you two leave, it'll get complicated.
You were the last to touch Su-ho.
I'll handle this. So just keep quiet.
Uh, what should we do?
["Again" by Han playing]
♪ I miss the memories, I miss your tune ♪
♪ It was only just yesterday
A chance to talk to you… ♪
[breathing unsteadily]
♪ It's summer already
Still, I don't know what to do… ♪
Su-ho. Su-ho. Su-ho-ya.
♪ How deep are you? No tracks to follow… ♪
[Beom-seok sobbing] Su-ho. Su-ho-ya.
- Su-ho! Su-ho-ya.
- ♪ How real am I ♪
♪ To face you hollow? ♪
Su-ho-ya, please look at me.
- ♪ Am I nothin' to you? ♪
- Let's go, Beom-seok-kun.
- We have to go, right now.
- Su-ho-ya! Hey!
- [sobbing]
- Beom-seok-kun.
- Hey, drag him out of here.
- [Beom-seok] What about Su-ho?
No, wait. He won't open his eyes.
What's going to happen to him?
- ♪ I feel my faith, my heart is racin'… ♪
- [Beom-seok sobbing]
Wait. Wait a minute.
- Wait, wait.
- ♪ I wanna dive into your warmth… ♪
[Yeong-i] Si-eun-a.
Where's Su-ho?
He's not here.
[sighs] He's not answering his phone.
Where did he go?
♪ Do you feel nothin'? ♪
- ♪ You must feel nothin'… ♪
- [ringing tone]
♪ My dear, it's time
For the hundredth time… ♪
[Yeong-i gasps]
♪ I finally do make up my mind… ♪
[ringing tone continues]
♪ It's time I lose you for good… ♪
[door slam echoing]
♪ I'm lost again ♪
[gentle, poignant
instrumental version of "Hero" playing]
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL